{
    "subject": "Paul_Auster",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Blue_in_the_Face",
    "human_readable": "Paul Auster created Blue in the Face.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8114656209945679,
            "question": "Who created the film Blue in the Face?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5629282593727112,
            "question": "Who might have starred in Blue in the Face?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5149518847465515,
            "question": "What themes might be explored in a film called Blue in the Face?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4594874083995819,
            "question": "Has Blue in the Face received any critical acclaim?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41501808166503906,
            "question": "What is the title of the film created by Paul Auster?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41025078296661377,
            "question": "Where and when was Blue in the Face likely filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3802209496498108,
            "question": "What genre might the film Blue in the Face belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2278371900320053,
            "question": "What is Paul Auster's background as a creative artist?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1854856312274933,
            "question": "Is Paul Auster known for writing or filmmaking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11981438845396042,
            "question": "Are there any other films by Paul Auster?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Paul Auster created Blue in the Face.",
            "html": "yago_27468_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Paul Auster known for writing or filmmaking?",
            "html": "yago_27468_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Paul Auster's background as a creative artist?",
            "html": "yago_27468_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre might the film Blue in the Face belong to?",
            "html": "yago_27468_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27468_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27468_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27468_139.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27468_159.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27468_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27468_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27468_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27468_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27468_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27468_67.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format for the query \"Paul Auster created Blue in the Face\":\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The text mentions that Paul Auster co-directed and wrote screenplays for \"Blue in the Face\", indicating his creative involvement with the film."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support that Paul Auster created or co-created the film \"Blue in the Face,\" as it is mentioned that he wrote the screenplay and was involved in its direction along with Wayne Wang."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}